{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334500647","data":{"timestamp":" 947334500646"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334501033","data":{"timestamp":" 947334501033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334501526","data":{"timestamp":" 947334501525"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334501882","data":{"timestamp":" 947334501882"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334502301","data":{"timestamp":" 947334502300"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334502787","data":{"timestamp":" 947334502786"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334503025","data":{"timestamp":" 947334503024"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334506227","data":{"timestamp":" 947334506226"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334506272","data":{"timestamp":" 947334506272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334506999","data":{"timestamp":" 947334506998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334507402","data":{"timestamp":" 947334507401"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334507708","data":{"timestamp":" 947334507708"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334507925","data":{"timestamp":" 947334507924"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334508130","data":{"timestamp":" 947334508130"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334508460","data":{"timestamp":" 947334508460"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334508696","data":{"timestamp":" 947334508696"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334511876","data":{"timestamp":" 947334511875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334512290","data":{"timestamp":" 947334512289"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334514892","data":{"timestamp":" 947334514891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334515105","data":{"timestamp":" 947334515105"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334515320","data":{"timestamp":" 947334515318"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334518856","data":{"timestamp":" 947334518855"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334522656","data":{"timestamp":" 947334522655"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334523690","data":{"timestamp":" 947334523690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334526419","data":{"timestamp":" 947334526418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334526810","data":{"timestamp":" 947334526809"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334527304","data":{"timestamp":" 947334527303"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334527654","data":{"timestamp":" 947334527653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334528071","data":{"timestamp":" 947334528070"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334528588","data":{"timestamp":" 947334528587"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334528824","data":{"timestamp":" 947334528823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334532221","data":{"timestamp":" 947334532220"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334532269","data":{"timestamp":" 947334532268"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334532998","data":{"timestamp":" 947334532997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334533404","data":{"timestamp":" 947334533403"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334533709","data":{"timestamp":" 947334533709"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334533931","data":{"timestamp":" 947334533930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334534137","data":{"timestamp":" 947334534136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334534464","data":{"timestamp":" 947334534463"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334534701","data":{"timestamp":" 947334534700"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334537339","data":{"timestamp":" 947334537336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947334537457","data":{"timestamp":" 947334537456"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000108_152803"," gameId":" d413312a-8a13-4d22-af31-52a1ad1ee512"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}